[
  {
    "question": "A sign overhead said Express eleven o'clock.",
    "location": 21,
    "answer": "A sign overhead said Hogwarts Express eleven o'clock."
  },
  {
    "question": "Professor rolled up her scroll and took the sorting hat away.",
    "location": 10,
    "answer": "Professor mcgonagall rolled up her scroll and took the sorting hat away."
  },
  {
    "question": "Hagrid came striding toward them out the dark fang at his heel.",
    "location": 37,
    "answer":  "Hagrid came striding toward them out of the dark fang at his heel."
  },
  {
    "question":  "In danger of being speared on the end of an umbrella by a bearded giant uncle courage failed again.",
    "location": 78,
    "answer":  "In danger of being speared on the end of an umbrella by a bearded giant uncle vernon courage failed again."
  },
  {
    "question":  "Gryffindor will in even more trouble.",
    "location": 16,
    "answer": "Gryffindor will be in even more trouble."
  },
  {
    "question":  "Soon there a huddle of limp black players slumped along the wall.",
    "location": 11,
    "answer": "Soon there was a huddle of limp black players slumped along the wall."
  },
  {
    "question":  "I m holding the house cup and the cup.",
    "location": 22,
    "answer": "I m holding the house cup and the quidditch cup"
  },
  {
    "question":  "Wingardium is a levitation charm.",
    "location": 11,
    "answer": "Wingardium leviosa is a levitation charm."
  },
  {
    "question":  "Harry looked behind him and saw a wrought iron archway where the barrier had been with the words platform and three quarters on it.",
    "location": 106,
    "answer": "Harry looked behind him and saw a wrought iron archway where the barrier had been with the words platform nine and three quarters on it."
  },
  {
    "question":  "Albus is the headmaster of the wizarding school hogwarts.",
    "location": 6,
    "answer": "Albus dumbledore is the headmaster of the wizarding school hogwarts."
  }]
